[{"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"These look fine to me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"look\", does the participant \"These\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"the guy came on time and did n't take any breaks , he went straight to work and finished the job efficiently and promptly !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"finished\", does the participant \"job\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We called our representative who assured me he would call the office and have it taken care of .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assured\", does the participant \"representative\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"A pattern of arrests and seizures indicate that arms are brought by the LTTE from Laos , Cambodia and Thailand into Chittagong , from where they are transported northward by land to Bhutan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"transported\", does the participant \"they\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I get that careless teenager kind of treatment from some of their staff ... perhaps they should hire more serious adults to help serve / cook .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"get\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They fixed the queso !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"They\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It 's located in the huge HONKA Log Homes building , by Walmart off of Evergreen Parkway .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"located\", does the participant \"It\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Mark Elliott tells me that you drafted some trader guidelines ( physical and financial ) for the London traders .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tells\", does the participant \"Elliott\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have no doubt that the civilized world will prevail .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The millions who died in the Iran - Iraq war had nothing to do with Israel .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"millions\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He described Allawi 's face as that of a f*ed horse and he dismissed the whole government as a band of thieves and traitors .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"described\", does the participant \"face\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"According to the Citizenship and Immigration Canada web site at http://www.cic.gc.ca/english/immigrate/skilled/assess/index.asp , it states \" Note : you must meet the minimum requirements for your application to be eligible for processing . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"meet\", does the participant \"requirements\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They needed someone that could convince the jury they had been able to see all relevant documents in CIA files on Wilson .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"convince\", does the participant \"someone\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Bangs said these animals are not equipped to survive in the wild , however , and they all almost certainly have died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"they\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They have unbeatable price in town and deliver on time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"They\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I think it is mine but I forgot to write it in the blue FX book ( I only wrote it in my red book ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wrote\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They picked my car up in Yarmouth and towed to Bath for a great price .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"picked\", does the participant \"car\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" There have no business being there unless they are undermining Pakistan , '' says a Pakistani official .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"undermining\", does the participant \"Pakistan\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A little birdie told me that you were checking into tickets for Seoul .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"checking\", does the participant \"you\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They need to update the locker rooms ASAP .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"update\", does the participant \"rooms\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" They filed an emergency motion , and we were not about to let California go dark , '' Hoecker said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Hoecker\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"India 's Andaman and Nicobar Islands comprise more than 500 islands lying 1,000 kilometers east of Sri Lanka in the Bay of Bengal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"comprise\", does the participant \"Islands\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Their screams changed , \" Dr. Fortier said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Fortier\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Robinson said the emergency order allowed the ISO to secure refunds should overcharges for electricity be proven to federal officials .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Robinson\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I use propane with a blower and a burner I built http://www.mikegigi.com/meltmetl.htm and http://www.mikegigi.com/firehole.htm\"\nQuestion: In the event \"built\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"One of the Wesley boys wrote the hymn .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wrote\", does the participant \"One\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Meats are kept VERY cold , seafood smells fresh and the serving bar is VERY clean .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"smells\", does the participant \"seafood\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"My nails looked great for the better part of 2 weeks !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"looked\", does the participant \"nails\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Attached are my resume and an addendum covering academic & consulting experience .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"resume\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"You need to check out the French Indochina War ( 1946 - 1954 ) not the Vietnam War ( 1957 - 1975 ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"check\", does the participant \"War\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I like music very loud and with a lot of bass .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"like\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have the following suggestion for our company .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"suggestion\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"At the time , guardsmen were required to accumulate a minimum of 50 points to meet their yearly obligation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"meet\", does the participant \"obligation\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They came on time and completed their work quickly .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"came\", does the participant \"They\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A state Senate committee is set today to start serving 16 subpoenas on electricity producers and officials who manage California 's energy grid to determine whether they acted in concert to manipulate energy prices .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"serving\", does the participant \"subpoenas\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Nervous people make mistakes , so I suppose there will be a wave of succesfull arab attacks .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"make\", does the participant \"mistakes\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The information contained herein is based on sources that we believe to be reliable , but we do not represent that it is accurate or complete .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"based\", does the participant \"information\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The dramatic increase in radiation - induced thyroid cancers in children and adolescents in Belarus , Russia , and Ukraine , which have been observed since 1991 , continues to this day .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"continues\", does the participant \"increase\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Grand - standing is ignored .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ignored\", does the participant \"standing\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"You said you liked her and she accepted it as a truth and perhaps as a compliment , but it does not mean she fancies you or wants to pair off with you .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accepted\", does the participant \"she\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Upon the same day he conquered Darius , won a great victory at sea , & died the same day .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"conquered\", does the participant \"Darius\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Guerrillas threatened to assassinate Prime Minister Iyad Allawi and Minister of Defense Hazem Shaalan in retaliation for the attack .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assassinate\", does the participant \"Allawi\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Dunn believes the resulting overcharges for electricity exceeded $ 30 billion .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"exceeded\", does the participant \"overcharges\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"i have a 1 and a half year old male neutered cat and a new 2 month old spayed female kitten .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"cat\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Musharraf told Clinton he could n't use Pakistani soil or air space to send the team in against Bin Laden .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"Musharraf\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Attached is PG&E 's Gas Accord II ( GA II ) Settlement Proposal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"Proposal\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I hope I can return the favor in the future !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"i use UTH's on all of my burrowing snakes .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"use\", does the participant \"i\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In Biloxi , 30 people were reported dead in one block of flats which was hit by a 9 m ( 30 ft ) \" storm surge \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reported\", does the participant \"people\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" ... there is no companion quite so devoted , so communicative , so loving and so mesmerizing as a rat . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"companion\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We attend LFTD and our children LOVE it !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"attend\", does the participant \"We\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The money funds their travel , explosives , hideouts and permanent search for soft vulnerable targets .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"funds\", does the participant \"money\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We took our beloved kitty to him and it came back dead .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"took\", does the participant \"We\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"rumor has feb 05 on the calender .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"rumor\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a concern that the Enron optionality bug could bite us on the backside with that one .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"concern\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Do n't get me wrong I want to go , but for 2 days -_- I mean seriously .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"mean\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They interviewed me , gave me tests in the software I included on my resume , and placed me in a position that I kept for several years .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"placed\", does the participant \"me\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Some board members pushed to have Winter removed , but there were concerns such action would lead to more chaos , the governor 's spokesman Maviglio said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"removed\", does the participant \"Winter\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"All of the doors tend to look alike and having ' something ' on your door helps you and your kids find your room easier .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tend\", does the participant \"All\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"That sounds like a BS excuse from ECS , but it that 's what they are saying , let me know and we can figure out a solution .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"figure\", does the participant \"we\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had no problem with my delivery .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"problem\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"i think Miramar was a famous goat trainer or something .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"i\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The First time I walked in there with my teacup chihuahua puppy I knew I 'd be here a lot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"walked\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"i want something cheap east to take care of and something to hopefully fit in my room\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"something\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"By comparison , outdoor cats have a life expectancy of 3 - 7 years depending on how many predators are in the local environment .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"cats\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Pioneers take a pledge to remain tee - total and at the hight of the organization popularity , had an estimated two million members even filling Croke Park on the 25th anniversary .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"take\", does the participant \"Pioneers\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have no doubt that the rescue is wonderful .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He said the main aim of the subpoenas will be to determine whether collusion occurred to \" fix \" prices , which would violate federal trade laws .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"violate\", does the participant \"laws\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It incorporates Mr. Stojic 's and Mr. Kelly 's initial comments .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"incorporates\", does the participant \"comments\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I hope you have found this information helpful .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Even Zawahiri 's attorney in 1999 said that Bin Laden and Zawahiri were likely to resort to the biological and chemical agents they possessed given the extradition pressure senior Al Qaeda leaders faced .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"attorney\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I wanted to be very blonde and instead he pulled my root color throughout my whole hair which is a gross mousey brown .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wanted\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"These animals have the misfortune to produce a substance that is useful in the manufacture of perfume .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"misfortune\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I suggest a \" blind draw \" on the teams , best ball not scramble on the golf , and as for the wager , no emails from the losing team for one week !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suggest\", does the participant \"draw\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I paid 2 k cash for a truck with a blown motor .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"paid\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"There are special regions uniquely and imposingly designed for the children .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the participant \"regions\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"EVERYTHING IN HERE SEEMS TO AMAZE ME !!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"SEEMS\", does the participant \"EVERYTHING\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"After 9/11 , Yazid Sufaat traveled to Afghanistan and Pakistan to work for the Taliban Medical Brigade and to continue his work with anthrax .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"traveled\", does the participant \"Sufaat\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I called them for an estimate and they INSULTED ME WHEN I ASK THEM QUESTIONS .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"INSULTED\", does the participant \"they\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I listed all of our ( sometimes mine vs. my wife 's favorites and priorities ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"listed\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In response to the rockets , Israel resumed its policy of targeting militant leaders in air strikes .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"resumed\", does the participant \"Israel\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I called in my order and upon arriving to pick it up , they got my order confused with someone else s .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Santa Claus has the right idea .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"Claus\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Yes , I say .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"say\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"US - trained Malaysian biochemist Yazid Sufaat met with 9/11 plotters and two hijackers in January 2000 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"met\", does the participant \"Sufaat\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The office refused my requests to see what they got from BC / BS .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"refused\", does the participant \"office\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A sender purporting to be islamist sent cyanide in both early 2002 and early 2003 in New Zealand and ingredients of nerve gas in Belgium in 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sent\", does the participant \"cyanide\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" The bear gave chase and I gave chase , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"he\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They asked us things that we would have never have thought of , and took extra time to meet with us when we needed it before the wedding .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the participant \"They\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They have unbeatable price in town and deliver on time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"price\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A team from the court managed to take his deposition before he died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"he\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Ben made another announcement on March 28 , 2005 :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"Ben\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"As first - time home buyers , my husband and I found Stephanie Fairchild at Prudential Steamboat Realty , extremely helpful .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"found\", does the participant \"husband\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The islamists sent letter bombs in January 1997 to newspaper offices in New York City and Washington , D.C. .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sent\", does the participant \"bombs\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We have a Full Color Catalog and Wholesale Price List ready to mail to you today !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"We\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The next day , the federal commission killed the new pricing plan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"plan\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There is NO such thing as a BTA .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"thing\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Mark Anderson says that even though Bondad gas flowed , the price was Non-Bondad .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"says\", does the participant \"Anderson\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Jim Lobe has more on the political implications of the Fallujah assault , both in Iraq and in Washington .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"more\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"From the delectable Antipasto Misto to the Spaghetti alla Barese and the Parmigiana and ending with gelato , all was mouth watering .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"watering\", does the participant \"all\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I wanted you all to have a look at what we believe is the final draft .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"we\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Cities such as Falluja received special treatment from Saddam and enjoyed a disproportionate share of the country 's wealth and power .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"received\", does the participant \"treatment\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I did the same thing that you did for christmas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My family loves coming to Endo Sushi . They are very nice , it is never crowded , and the food is wonderful , very delicious and fresh !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"loves\", does the participant \"family\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My boyfriend and I were woken up in the middle of the night at our campsite by drunken kids who 'd arrived around 1:00 am and were drinking at the springs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"woken\", does the participant \"boyfriend\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I wish that I had n't done this .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I was amazed at the spiel they delivered .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"delivered\", does the participant \"they\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"'' It was the first time that Bush totally focused on the Taliban threat rather than Al Qaeda with the Pakistanis , '' says a Western diplomat .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"focused\", does the participant \"Bush\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I drafted the Into TVA Option as a series of calls tied to the MOPA delivery term and quantity - not sure if this anything close to what you all had in mind .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"drafted\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He earned 137 points in 1970 - 1971 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"earned\", does the participant \"He\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think this place is probably really great especially judging by the reviews on here .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"One thought is to have just the agenda as a couple topics and then lead in with the first two questions as I 've listed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"listed\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Only Caucasians had any political power , corporate presence or owned businesses except for Mom and Pop stores in some neighborhoods .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"power\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The thing about The Script is they do not sound that Irish , I was surprised to hear they were from Dublin .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"thing\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They sell feed and milk bottles at the front and I recommend you buy lots .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"buy\", does the participant \"you\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We love Little Farmer\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"Farmer\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"( Newsweek reported that Bush commanded his cabinet , \" Let heads roll ! \" )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"commanded\", does the participant \"Bush\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I knew what it was and told the guy that it was n't a fps .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"knew\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They said they were \" unable to tell me until they ordered my dress \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the participant \"dress\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They indicated they could use Steve 's help face to face at some point .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"indicated\", does the participant \"They\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a friend out in Chicago this week , and I am trying to remember the name of an awesome hibachi style restaurant i visited while out there a couple years ago .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"visited\", does the participant \"i\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"the guy came on time and did n't take any breaks , he went straight to work and finished the job efficiently and promptly !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"came\", does the participant \"guy\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"they use them to look prickly .. would you try to eat a cactus [ if u had no knife ] i know i would nt .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"use\", does the participant \"them\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I moved to Creekside Apartments in August 2008 with a 6 - month lease and have just extended it for another 13 months !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"extended\", does the participant \"it\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A Yellowstone wolf was found dead , hit by a car , on a Colorado highway last year , several hundred miles from home .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"found\", does the participant \"wolf\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They want to use LTS to tie into NASA 's vision for Space Exploration , and seem pleased that the White House is moving in that direction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"They\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Civet cats are trapped and placed in small cages inside darkened sheds , where the temperature is kept up to 110 F by fires .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"trapped\", does the participant \"cats\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"JUNO AND OPEN I LOVE YOU GUYS !!!!!!!!!!!!!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"LOVE\", does the participant \"YOU\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"All you want is for \" them \" to get on with it - and to leave you alone ..\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"All\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Musk , which is scraped from their genitals once a day for as long as they can surv ive , makes the scent of perfume last a bit longer after each application .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"makes\", does the participant \"Musk\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I found this on a bulletin board and decided to try it : I do n't care about the useless pre-fabricated crap this message usually says .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"found\", does the participant \"this\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Doug and I met with the Chairman of PUCT and have had subsequent conversations .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"met\", does the participant \"Doug\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The dealer wanted $ 1300 to fix that and another $ 1500 to fix some other things .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wanted\", does the participant \"$\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"A pattern of arrests and seizures indicate that arms are brought by the LTTE from Laos , Cambodia and Thailand into Chittagong , from where they are transported northward by land to Bhutan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"brought\", does the participant \"arms\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I hope you have a great summer .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"YOU GET WHAT YOU PAY FOR !!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"PAY\", does the participant \"YOU\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Some countries like Malaysia and Singapore promote trading for foreign visitors during some part of the year .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"promote\", does the participant \"countries\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"His family loves him .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"loves\", does the participant \"family\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I guess if you have a schtick that is a resounding success once , you ca n't help but trot it out every time your act is going sour .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"guess\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" We believe the action we took addressed a severe concern , '' Robinson said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Robinson\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Yet people seem willing -- even eager -- to accommodate mountain lions , despite the risks .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accommodate\", does the participant \"lions\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The civilized world believes in democracy , the rule of law , including international law , human rights , free speech and free press , among other liberties .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believes\", does the participant \"world\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The work was completed within one week , and everything was cleaned up on completion .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"completed\", does the participant \"work\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They wanted to brainwash them and control them . ''\"\nQuestion: In the event \"brainwash\", does the participant \"them\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The initial reservoir reports estimate reserves of 80 - 120 million barrels of sour crude and they estimate initial production to be 40,000 bpd starting in 1Q 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"estimate\", does the participant \"reports\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I enjoyed my tour and i am looking for adventure tour and India heritage tours for valuable .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enjoyed\", does the participant \"tour\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He showed me the car I was interested in and we took a test drive .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"showed\", does the participant \"He\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I revised the language based on our discussions and added the language concerning interest which we had both previously approved .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"revised\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Blue cross has no record of aa reversal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"cross\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I assume you mean the crazy horse memorial .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"mean\", does the participant \"you\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A girl raises her hand .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"raises\", does the participant \"hand\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The name was derived from the founder 's name Dr. Michael Cowpland .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"derived\", does the participant \"name\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This place had the worst tasting pizza I have ever tasted it was possible the worst food I 've ever eaten .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tasted\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I asked her who she worked with and she just told me ti was the sales manager .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I knew a cat that died in its sleep aged 21 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"knew\", does the participant \"cat\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They LOVE to climb .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"LOVE\", does the participant \"They\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This means that I could be away from the office for several days and miss a message entirely , because it would have expired and disappeared by the time I returned .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"miss\", does the participant \"message\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Yesterday evening , the Posada story was featured in the public television news show in Germany ( ARD , Tagesthemen ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"featured\", does the participant \"ARD\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Several candidates were assassinated and targeted these last two weeks , others have been forced under threats to withdraw and to follow the example of the Islamic party .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"forced\", does the participant \"others\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Prices for electricity jumped from an average of $ 249 a megawatt to $ 700 a megawatt within three days , ISO records show .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"jumped\", does the participant \"Prices\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Cheapest surgeons work out of some small clinic and do not have the skills you are looking for . .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"work\", does the participant \"surgeons\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We need to change the lock and place posted signs at the gate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"place\", does the participant \"signs\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"she knows she is invading someone else 's territory , but ca n't help it , and has no where to go .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"invading\", does the participant \"she\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have no complaints about the service I received .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"complaints\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Al - Sharq al - Awsat reports that a key eyewitness in the trial of Saddam Hussein for a 1982 massacre at Dujail has died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"eyewitness\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Guerrillas near Hawijah launched an attack that left 6 dead , including 4 Iraqi soldiers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"launched\", does the participant \"Guerrillas\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"** Google defies US over search data **\"\nQuestion: In the event \"defies\", does the participant \"US\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Requests like that were n't unusual , says retired Col. William Campenni , who flew with Bush in 1970 and 1971 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"says\", does the participant \"Campenni\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We came at around 730 and they close at 8 and wanted to try the specials but they were out for the day so I would say go way before they close .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"came\", does the participant \"We\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We had an inside cabin and it is what I would recommend .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"cabin\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Syria is surrounded by Turkey , Iraq , Jordan and Israel .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"surrounded\", does the participant \"Syria\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I think it was in the Lincoln Square area but do n't quote me on that .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Another problem is that sometimes bad eggs will fungus and the fungus will spread out and kill all the eggs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kill\", does the participant \"eggs\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Xinhua alleged that \" Many of the Iraqis , who suffer the American occupation of Iraq , relate their case with that of the Palestinian people , under the Israeli occupation . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"relate\", does the participant \"Many\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" At some point , Patricia tripped or the bear tripped her and was at her back .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tripped\", does the participant \"her\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"She had her cards memorized as well as everyone else s ( when you play you 'll see why you can know everyone else s hands ! ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"play\", does the participant \"you\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The initial reservoir reports estimate reserves of 80 - 120 million barrels of sour crude and they estimate initial production to be 40,000 bpd starting in 1Q 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"estimate\", does the participant \"they\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" He left a message for everyone to see ... maybe to God himself . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the participant \"He\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Linda Robertson says they should be charged to Jim Steffes ' cost center , etc .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"says\", does the participant \"Robertson\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I doubt you will get a sensible answer in the \" TRAVEL \" section .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"doubt\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Police in the Indian capital Delhi say they have arrested the suspected co-ordinator and financier of last month 's deadly bomb blasts in the city .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arrested\", does the participant \"co-ordinator\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I expected to pay for this service , but imagine my surprise when I received a bill for MORE than what I paid to have the original return prepared .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"paid\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We love our new roof !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"We\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Some refused to leave , but so many were unable to .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"refused\", does the participant \"Some\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I love it for discounted beauty items and household appliances .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"it\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"During his time in the Guard , George Bush flew the F - 102 Delta Dagger fighter - interceptor .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"flew\", does the participant \"Bush\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We have and will have children of our own , grandchildren too .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"children\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Attached are the draft Schedule to the ISDA Master Agreement , together with Paragraph 13 to the ISDA Credit Support Annex .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"Schedule\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Debbie said , it is going to be hard on me to sale my old dodge truck .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sale\", does the participant \"truck\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Denial of the status of marriage to those who would freely accept its responsibilities creates legal and economic inequities and social injustice .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"creates\", does the participant \"inequities\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"MFJ Inc transformed our run down back yard into a place of beauty .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"transformed\", does the participant \"Inc\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In a bulletin , the FBI noted that the surveillance might relate to a plot to disperse a chemical or biological weapon .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"noted\", does the participant \"FBI\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In response to the rockets , Israel resumed its policy of targeting militant leaders in air strikes .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"targeting\", does the participant \"leaders\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Last week , Federal District Judge Lynn Hughes in Huston , Texas , threw out Wilson 's two - decades old conviction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"threw\", does the participant \"Hughes\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a kitten who just turned 3 months today .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"kitten\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Joe removed a wasp nest for our condominium building and we appreciated the environmentally friendly method and prompt , friendly and informative service .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"removed\", does the participant \"nest\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I got this .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The Americans detected the attempt to infiltrate the urban areas and were already redeploying troops from the rural areas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"detected\", does the participant \"attempt\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I believe he must have waited among the gorse bushes through which the path winds and struck him down as he passed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"struck\", does the participant \"him\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I think you may be adhering to it too faithfully .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"adhering\", does the participant \"you\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}]